（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)
您好，欢迎来到您全新的课程，
Hello, and welcome to your brand new course,
使用 HTML 和 CSS 构建响应式真实世界的网站。
build responsive real-world websites with HTML and CSS.
如果这是你的第一次接触
And if this is your very first contact
使用任何 HTML 或 CSS 编码，
with any coding of HTML or CSS,
那么让我也欢迎你
then let me also welcome you
到令人兴奋的 Web 开发世界。
to the exciting world of web development.
我相信你会喜欢的。
I'm sure that you're gonna love it.
现在正如课程名称所说，
Now as the name of the course says,
本课程是关于使用 HTML 和 CSS 的语言
this course is all about using the languages of HTML and CSS
构建美观、响应迅速且真实世界的网站。
to build beautiful, responsive, and also real world website.
所以这门课程基本上涵盖了四大主题，
And so this course basically covers four big topics,
网页设计、HTML 和 CSS，当然，
web design, HTML, and CSS, of course,
和响应式设计。
and responsive design.
在我看来，这门课程，
And this course is in my opinion,
学习这一切的最好方法
the very best way of learning all this
你会在任何地方找到。
that you will find anywhere.
所以你真的来对地方了。
And so really you have come to the right place here.
现在，在我们开始学习之前，
Now, before we start learning,
让我们花几分钟时间快速了解一下
let's take a couple of minutes to get a quick overview
课程的组织和结构，
of how the course is organized and structured,
以及我们将共同建设的项目。
and also the projects that we're going to build together.
所以基本上你知道
So basically that, you know exactly
这门课程将如何运作。
how this course is gonna work.
所以本课程分为九个部分
So this course is divided into nine sections
总共 35 小时的视频内容。
with a total of 35 hours of video content.
它从第一节开始
And it starts right here in section one
您将在其中获得高级概述
where you will get a high-level overview
Web 开发的一般，它也将构建
of web development general, and it will also build
您非常快速但非常简单的网页，
your very fast, but extremely simple webpage,
只是为了让您对即将发生的事情感到兴奋。
just to get you excited for what's ahead.
然后在第二部分，我们要搬家
Then in section two, we're gonna move
HTML 语言的基础知识
to the very basics of the HTML language
通过构建一个小项目，
by building a small project,
为您接下来的课程打下坚实的基础。
to give you a solid foundation for the rest of the course.
在第三节之后，
After that in section number three,
你将学习 CSS 的基础。
you're gonna learn the foundations of CSS.
所以像样式文本、CSS 框模型、
So things like styling text, the CSS box model,
以及尺寸和定位元素。
and sizing and positioning elements.
我们甚至会讨论一些开发人员的技能
And we will even talk about some developer skills
比如阅读文档和调试。
such as reading documentation and debugging.
继续前进，第四部分是关于
Moving on, section number four is all about
使用 CSS 构建布局。
building layouts using CSS.
所以基本上是关于如何排列元素
So basically it's about how to arrange elements
以合乎逻辑的方式在页面上。
on the page in a logical way.
我们可以在 CSS 中以多种方式做到这一点。
And we can do that in multiple ways in CSS.
所以我们将学习所有这些，
And so we will learn all of them,
但实际上更多地关注现代技术
but actually focus more on modern technologies
称为 Flexbox 和 CSS 网格。
called Flexbox and CSS grid.
然后在第五节，
Then in section five,
我们从 Web 开发中稍作休息
we take a small break from web development
并继续进行网页设计。
and move on to web design.
这实际上是一个非常特别的部分，
And this is actually a really special section,
这实际上可能是一个完整的课程。
which could infact be an entire course on its own.
所以在这里我教你无数好用的设计法则
So here I teach you countless easy to use design rules
和设计指南，
and design guidelines,
这样您不仅可以构建接口，
so that you can not only build interfaces,
但也知道如何让它们变得美丽
but also know how to make them beautiful
和专业的外观。
and professional looking.
而且人其实并不多
And there are actually not many people
同时擅长开发和设计的人。
who are good at development and design at the same time.
所以这部分课程
And so this part of the course
对你来说将是一个很好的机会。
is gonna be a great opportunity for you.
接下来是第六节，
Next up is section six,
我们将在这里学习所有常见的网站组件
where we will learn all about common website components
以及许多网站使用的常见布局模式，
and common layout patterns that many websites out there use,
这样你就可以n 将来建立自己的网站
so that then you can build your own websites in the future
也使用这些模式。
using these patterns too.
我们将通过查看大量示例来做到这一点
And we will do this by looking at a ton of examples
并且还通过构建一些组件
and also by building some components
我们自己使用 HTML 和 CSS。
with HTML and CSS ourselves.
最后，第七、八、九节
Finally, section seven, eight, and nine
都是关于建筑或大型课程项目，
are all about building or big course project,
这就是所谓的Omnifood。
which is called Omnifood.
所以在这里，我们最终将构建那个漂亮的、响应式的
So here we will finally build that beautiful, responsive
和本课程所涉及的真实世界网站。
and real world website that this course is all about.
要做到这一点，你将使用所有的技能
And to do this, you're gonna use all the skills
你已经积累到这一点。
that you have accumulated up until this point.
当然也学到了很多新东西
And of course also learn a lot of new stuff
例如如何规划和绘制一个网站，
such as how to plan and sketch a website,
如何让它响应
how to make it responsive
以及真正如何处理这么大的项目
and really how to handle such a big project
从开始到结束。
from start to finish.
所以只要看看这个美丽的项目就在这里。
So just look at this beautiful project right here.
在课程结束时，
By the end of the course,
你将能够设计和建造
you will be able to design and build
像这样的事情你自己。
something just like this on your own.
这真是太神奇了，对吧？
And that is just amazing, right?
现在，除了这一切，
Now, besides all this,
还有许多编码挑战
there are also many coding challenges
以及其他机会
and also other opportunities
为您练习 HTML 和 CSS 技能
for you to practice the HTML and CSS skills
您在本课程中不断获得的
that you keep acquiring over the course of this course
因为练习实际上是
because practicing is actually
最重要的事情
the single most important thing
为了学习编码，您确实需要这样做。
that you really need to do in order to learn coding.
好吧，所以我希望你会玩得开心
All right, so I hope that you're gonna have a ton of fun
现在你将成为这门课程
with this course now that you'll become
准备建立自己的网站
ready to build your own websites
并且你将有一个成功的开始
and that you will have a successful start
进入您的 Web 开发生涯。
into your web development career.
话虽如此，
And with that being said,
让我们现在终于开始了。
let's now finally get started.
（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)